<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wrde Of The Day</title>
    <link>https://www.wrdeoftheday.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Wrde Of The Day</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 08:18:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.wrdeoftheday.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Campsies</title>
      <link>https://www.wrdeoftheday.co.uk/cycling/the-campsies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 08:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.wrdeoftheday.co.uk/cycling/the-campsies/</guid>
      <description>Cycling around the Campsies A 50 km loop that includes the Crow Road and Tak-Ma-Doon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Brass</title>
      <link>https://www.wrdeoftheday.co.uk/music/great-brass/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 20:50:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.wrdeoftheday.co.uk/music/great-brass/</guid>
      <description>A collection of great brass tunes This is a curated list of music that features great brass.
I can’t find a recording of Overture Promenade by Frank Bryce but this video is really good:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CI for LaTex</title>
      <link>https://www.wrdeoftheday.co.uk/posts/ci_for_latex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 19:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.wrdeoftheday.co.uk/posts/ci_for_latex/</guid>
      <description>How to use bitbucket pipelines to generate LaTex documents Why do this? It’s a handy way to have LaTex documents on the go and collaboration.
Docker container The typical way of installing LaTex is texlive and one would normally install the full version. Whilst, this is great it is pretty big. So I have created a container with a basic LaTex installation: https://hub.docker.com/r/wrdeman/docker-min-tex This may or may not meet your requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://www.wrdeoftheday.co.uk/posts/django-benchmark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2019 21:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.wrdeoftheday.co.uk/posts/django-benchmark/</guid>
      <description>Concurrency, Django and Apache Bench The motivation for this blog was as a starting point in debugging errors caused errors caused by concurrency or race conditions - the so-called Heisenbug. I am going to use a contrived example of a bank account with a method to withdraw money and record each transaction. Then I will make a number of concurrent requests and investigate any undesired effects. I do not, in this blog, seek to propose any solution to these effects - solely to provide a means of determining whether they are present.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Average House Prices</title>
      <link>https://www.wrdeoftheday.co.uk/posts/average-house-prices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 20:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.wrdeoftheday.co.uk/posts/average-house-prices/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s the average house price in a school&amp;rsquo;s catchment area? In order to calculate the average house price in a school&amp;rsquo;s catchment area, we are going to use PostGIS and OpenStreetMap. We&amp;rsquo;ll need to know the price and location of houses sold in that area, and the location of the schools and it&amp;rsquo;s catchment area. The former can be determined from the land registry and although this does not provide any geocoding we can do this using data provided by OpenStreetMap&amp;rsquo;s Nominatim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.wrdeoftheday.co.uk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.wrdeoftheday.co.uk/about/</guid>
      <description>Me Physicist I started life as a physicist with a focus in understanding semiconductors lasers with the aim of making them efficient. As time passed I became more interested in making lasers do wierd and wonderful things - emitting two colors at once and acting as an optical RAM. All my publications are here.
Developer Moving on&amp;hellip; After cutting it as a physicist, I decided to follow my dream of becoming a professional coder.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>